(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
hololive production COUNTDOWN LIVE 2025-2026
ホロライブファンクラブ！
hololive Official Fan Club!
一条莉々華だよ！
I'm Ichijou Ririka!
I'm Mori Calliope.
ホロライブファンクラブ、始めました！
We've started the hololive Official Fan Club!
ここだけのオリジナルグッズや、チケット先行抽選、
Exclusive original goods, advance ticket lotteries,
他にも楽しいコンテンツがいっぱい！
and lots of other fun content!
Campaign too? That sounds really fun! I'm curious.
さあ、みんな！
Come on, everyone!
ホロライブファンクラブで一緒に楽しもう！
Let's have fun together in the hololive Official Fan Club!
Join us now!
hololive production OFFICIAL POP-UP SHOP
再販 ゆくホロくるホロ年末年始デートボイス 〜ゆくホロ2023！〜
[Resale] YukuHolo KuruHolo Year-End/New Year Date Voice ~YukuHolo 2023!~
ここは露天風呂が有名だっていうから、ずっと気になってたんだよね〜！
I heard this place is famous for its open-air baths, so I've been curious about it for a long time!
ね、君も一緒に行かない？
Hey, won't you come with me?
えっ！？一緒に入るって意味じゃないよ！
Eh!? I don't mean we should enter together!
おーそーじ！
Big, big cleanup!
モココ、大掃除をやってみたいんだよね！
Mococo wants to try doing the big cleanup!
もちろん君も一緒にやるんだよ！？
Of course, you'll be doing it with me too, right!?
じゃあ、早速大掃除、開始だ〜！
Well then, let's start the big cleanup right away!
え〜？服のすきまがどうしたって〜？
Eh~? What's wrong with the gap in my clothes~?
僕が掃除している間に、君はいったいどこを見てたのかな〜？
While I was cleaning, I wonder where on earth you were looking~?
お〜！ここが夢にまで見た、日本の温泉街〜♪
Wow~! This is the Japanese hot spring town I've been dreaming of~♪
ん？もしかして......私と一緒に入りたいなとか、思ってる？
Hmm? By any chance... are you hoping to enter with me?
......いいよ、一緒に入ろっか......？
...Sure, shall we enter together...?
って、やばいやばい！みんな、そろそろカウントダウン始まるよ！
Wait, this is bad! Everyone, the countdown is about to start!
5、4、3、2、1、0！
5, 4, 3, 2, 1, 0!
ハッピーニューイヤー！
Happy New Year!
あけましておめでとうございます！今年もよろしくお願いします！
Happy New Year! I look forward to working with you again this year!
えへへ......なんか改めてかしこまると、はずかしくて照れちゃうね♪
Ehehe... Being formal like this makes me feel a bit embarrassed and shy♪
ダイヤモンド富士っていうんだっけ？
Is it called Diamond Fuji?
ほらほら！だんだん富士山の輪郭が見えてきたよ！
Look, look! The outline of Mount Fuji is gradually appearing!
なんだかもう、この景色だけで感動するよ〜！
Somehow, just this scenery alone is so moving~!
突然ですが、おせちを作りまーす！
This is sudden, but I'll be making osechi!
つまみ食いしちゃだめだよ？
No sneak eating, okay?
もしつまみ食いしちゃったら......ガブってしちゃうからねっ！
If you do sneak a bite... I'll bite you!
おめでとー！おめでとー！キミとぎゅーしながらお祝い♪
Happy New Year! Happy New Year! Celebrating while hugging you♪
キミをぎゅーできるのはモココだけなんだから！
Because only Mococo can hug you!
ほらほら、キミもモココのことぎゅーっとして！
Come on, you hug Mococo too!
せーの！
Ready, set...
今年もよろしくお願いします！
We look forward to another great year with you!
ときのそら TOKINO SORA
Tokino Sora
夢の途中の
In the middle of a dream...
一瞬一瞬を、
...each and every moment...
一緒に大切に。
...let's treasure them together.
過去最大規模の
The largest-scale...
「そらぱ」がいま始まる。
...\"Sorapa\" begins now.
ホロライブ3期生！
Hololive 3rd Generation!
次に挑む舞台は、
The next stage they will challenge is...
大作戦！？
...a major operation?!
ホロライブ3期生ライブ！「#きゅるるん大作戦」〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜
hololive 3rd Generation Live! #Kyururun Daisakusen ~The strongest idols, you have no choice but to support them~
「好き」と「かわいい」を詰め込んであなたと作る大作戦！
A major operation packed with \"love\" and \"cute\" to create together with you!
いっぱいのこれまでと、ときめくような一瞬を！
All of our \"up until now\", and moments that make your heart flutter!
どこまででも行けちゃう気がする！
I feel like we can go absolutely anywhere!
ちなみに作戦の内容は...とにかく可愛い！可愛いに満たされろ！
By the way, the details of the operation are... anyway, cute! Be filled with cuteness!
作戦進行中！
Operation in progress!
This is FLOW GLOW in countdown live! 来年もよろしくー！
This is FLOW GLOW in Countdown Live! Look forward to next year too!
搭載v8エンジン
Packin' a V8 engine
第7感持ってる原人
And a seventh sense for things
6するこの世界と全人類
Six ways to Sunday, this world and all humanity
この5人でゲームをチェンジ
With us five, we change the game
唸る4輪発射セヨ
Fire up the roaring four wheels
皆さん3キューサランヘヨ
Thank you all three-fold, saranghae yo
操る2台のturntable
Spinning two turntables
獲る1番ここground 0
Becoming number one, starting here, Ground Zero
リスク超えて挑戦
Face the risks and stand up
チャンスもセットだ当然
Chances naturally come as a set
登り上げる頂点
Going to the top, all the way up
座布団積んでく笑点
Stacking cushions like Shoten
乗り込むfg roadster
Jumping into an FG Roadster
特殊部隊集合能力者
We got a special unit full of espers
この歴史に名を彫る彫刻家
Sculptors carving our names in history
ぶっちぎりで置き去り後続車
Leaving any slower cars in the dust
今高速でぶち抜けていく大気圏
Speeding through the stratosphere at high speed
エンジンからジェットの炎揺れている怪気炎
Our jet engines' thrusting flame is roaring
眼下に広がる大地を越えていく回帰線
Crossing the tropics over the expanding earth below
バックミラーにbig blueが写っているibm
Seeing the big blue in the rearview, IBM
打ち上げ台から飛んでく
Taking off from the launch pad
うちら世代この燃料
This fuel is for our generation
朽ち果てないです銀河で
We won't decay in the galaxy
寿司食べたい
I wanna eat sushi
見えてるでかいビジョン
We got a massive vision in sight
燃えてるメンバー一同
All of us burning with passion
ただいま現在進行形
And as of this moment, actively progressing
超えてく世界規模
Going above and beyond on a global scale
叶うはずだwon't stop
Dreams come true, we won't stop
心臓がモンスター
Our hearts are a monster
aliens turn it up
fg party hard
光るtesla roadster
Shining Tesla Roadster
heavy booster
目覚めていく本能 青い炎
Awakening our instincts, blue flame
bff let's go out, so get in the car
0から宇宙まで囚われず
Unshackled from zero to the universe
走るfg roadster
Speeding the FG Roadster
唸るbooster
Roaring booster
flow glow the space to be
今chase me
Now chase me
ターボ付きスーパーカー
A turbocharged supercar
ハンドル捌きはシューマッハ
And handling like Schumacher
副操縦士はチューバッカ
Co-driver is Chewbacca
次元が違う連中ばっか
Just a bunch of folks from a different dimension
コーナー攻めてるギリギリ
Braking at the last minute
モーター全開地響き
Motors at full throttle, shaking the ground
空から導き
A lead from the sky
お肌がピチピチ
Our skin is so bouncy
タイヤ焦がしてドーナツターン
Tires smoking during a donut turn
弾け飛んでくドラム缶
Sending barrels flying up
顧客満足度高くて
High customer satisfaction
ぶち上がってるお客さん
Crowd is going nuts
0から最高到達点
Going from zero to the highest peak
ためてる太陽光発電
Charged up on solar power
探索するこの小惑星
Exploring this asteroid
超覚醒突入ボーナスステージ
Hit the super-awakened bonus stage
一直線伸びてる道路
A road stretching in a straight line
vibrationエンジンの鼓動
Vibration, the engine's heartbeat
速度増し上がってる高度
Speed going up, rising altitude
限界、重力、凌駕し上昇
Shaking off our limits and gravity, we soar
開拓しまくってくフロンティア
Terraforming the frontier
旅立つroadster only one
The roadster is the only pioneer
アクセル踏み込んでくドンピシャ
Putting the pedal to the metal with perfect timing
飛んでく日本遺産
Flying past Japanese heritages
1億馬力の重低音
The bass packs a billion horsepower
火星のホテルが休憩所
A hotel on Mars is our rest room
並んで走行ufo
As the UFOs race in space
降り立つ宇宙ステーション
Landing on the space station
物語を継承
Continuing the story
まるで旧約聖書
Like the Old Testament
この先何世紀も成長
For centuries, we'll have all the glory
生き延びて結果出すtake off
To survive and make our mark, take off!
叶うはずだwon't stop
Dreams come true, we won't stop
心臓がモンスター
Our hearts are a monster
aliens turn it up
fg party hard
光るtesla roadster
Shining Tesla Roadster
heavy booster
目覚めていく本能 青い炎
Awakening our instincts, blue flame
bff let's go out, so get in the car
0から宇宙まで囚われず
Unshackled from zero to the universe
走るfg roadster
Speeding the FG Roadster
唸るbooster
Roaring booster
GLORY GLORY the space for me
今 Chase me
Now chase me!
以上、私たちReGLOSSでした！
That's all from us, ReGLOSS!
こっから先も、楽しんでいこう！
Let's keep having fun from here on out too!
Tame the fire and fall before my justice
Final warning, you know my rage is limitless
On the advent of a new genesis
I'm infamous, yeah, I get a little villainous
Look into my eyes, I'll take you on a rebel ride
Truth and lies that you just can't hide
Clawing at the walls, I feel these sick temptations
What do I have to sacrifice?
Bound by a chain, desiring to do it my way
This hurricane of a devastating force is coming
Out of my veins, feel my pulse, it's rising and igniting
Fire!
Snuff it out
Walking the line, on the edge of becoming
what I never thought I'd be
Better this than a goner
Take 'em all out, Renegade!
Walking the line, fell so far into poison
and I'm seeing me anew
Got ya, locked and I'm loaded
Take 'em all out, Renegade!
Justice, it's just like that, I...
Don't care at all, I'll fall deeper 'til I can't quit
Never gon' stop 'cause I don't have a limit
My moral compass is out of focus
Renegade, I'll make it a little wicked
The light goes out! Huh!
The light goes out!
The light goes out! Ha!
Make 'em fall down, make your, make your last wish
Make 'em, make 'em fall down, then they crash
Renegade, I'll make 'em
Make 'em fall down, make your, make your last wish
Make 'em, make 'em fall down, then they crash
Renegade, I'll make 'em
Bound by a vow, can I tread the waters lightly
Never making a sound, incognito, light the pathway
Burning 'em out, in the fallout I'll stand in the ashes
Fire!
Snuff it out
Walking the line, on the edge of becoming
what I never thought I'd be
Better this than a goner
Take 'em all out, Renegade!
Walking the line, fell so far into poison
and I'm seeing me anew
Got ya, locked and I'm loaded
Take 'em all out, Renegade!
Justice, it's just like that, I...
Don't care at all, I'll fall deeper 'til I can't quit
Never gon' stop 'cause I don't have a limit
My moral compass is out of focus
Renegade, I'll make it a little wicked
The light goes out! Huh!
The light goes out!
The light goes out! Ha!
Tame the fire and fall before my justice
Final warning, you know my rage is limitless
On the advent of a new genesis
I'm infamous, yeah, I get a little villainous
The light goes out
空覚えで挑む人生ゲーム
Playing the game of life by ear
言い訳めいたハートに従って
Following a heart that seems full of excuses
現実は半即興なプロットです
Reality is a semi-improvised plot
取り憑かれるオーバーな芝居
Possessed by an over-the-top performance
世渡り上手なあの子はね
That girl who knows how to get by in life, you see...
二度と被った猫外せない
Can never take off the friendly facade she put on
痛みを知ってしまったmagician
The magician who has come to know pain
手の内は未だ明かせない
Still can't reveal their hand
yellow yellow ゼロからループ
Yellow yellow, looping from zero
点滅するピリオド
A flashing period
yellow yellow 染まる紅い化粧
Yellow yellow, stained with red makeup
I wonder if I can make it or not
たとえツキに見放されても
Even if I'm abandoned by luck
No worries
私には私がついてる
I have myself with me
宵が醒めるまであと少しだけ
Just a little more until the night wakes up
真のi捕える残像
A true image captured, a lingering illusion
Slow and steady wins the race
次の季節を越え blooming blooming
Crossing into the next season, blooming, blooming
どうかこの音を止めないで
Please don't stop this sound
Hourtime yellow, yellow Let it blow, let it blow ずっとstay gold
Hourtime yellow, yellow, let it blow, let it blow, always stay gold
Hourtime yellow, yellow Let it blow, let it blow
Let's enjoy the moment
Look into the mirror
絡まってる蜘蛛の糸
Spider threads tangled up
It happens all the time
踊らされたって構わない
I don't mind being made to dance
夜を日に継いで時を編んで明け暮れて
Connecting night to day, weaving time, through dawn and dusk
Always be honest
永遠に変わらないもの
Something that will never change
Yellow, yellow 手をとり合えばそこに理由はいらない
Yellow, yellow, if we hold hands, no reason is needed
Yellow, yellow 染まる紅い化粧
Yellow, yellow, stained with red makeup
A smile suits you best
幾つになってもchangeless
Changeless no matter how old I get
希望夢は人知れず
Hopes and dreams, unknown to others
歪で数奇な運命や
Even distorted and strange fates
人生ごと受け入れる
I accept life as it is
心機一転 二転 三転 詠んで第五感でlock on
Turning over a new leaf, flipping, lock on with the fifth sense
右見て左見てpause前だけ向いてgo on
Look right, look left, pause, facing only forward, go on
歌い続ける24/7
Singing 24/7
終着地点はeden or heaven?
Is the final destination Eden or heaven?
No time to waste
今だけを信じてる
I only believe in 'now'
最後のフィナーレまで共に進め
Proceed together until the final finale
宵が醒めるまであと少しだけ
Just a little more until the night wakes up
真のi捕える残像
A true image captured, a lingering illusion
Slow and steady wins the race
次の季節を越え blooming blooming
Crossing into the next season, blooming, blooming
どうかこの音を止めないで
Please don't stop this sound
Hourtime yellow, yellow Let it blow, let it blow ずっとstay gold
Hourtime yellow, yellow, let it blow, let it blow, always stay gold
Hourtime yellow, yellow Let it blow, let it blow
Let's enjoy the moment
お疲れ様でしたー！
Thank you very much!
楽しかったー！
That was fun!
ReGLOSSでした、バイバーイ！
We were ReGLOSS! Bye-bye!
Time to open up your eyes
Feel the music start to rise
Got to break the world and let me in
I know I was meant to be
Livin' life so fast and free
Try to keep your eyes on me
'Cause this is where my story all begins
Livin' it up like crazy
Ready to play? Come at me
Carried away so easy
...bow-bow-bow-bow
Tell me how you like me now?
Let's celebrate the New Year!
Watch me, watch me, watch me
Let your worries go, gonna show you how to lose control
You've got to free your mind
Leave your restraint behind
Be outrageous, the chaos is contagious
Come on, you know what time it is
It's our Genesis!
Time to open up your eyes
Feel the music start to rise
Got to break the world and let me in
I know I was meant to be
Livin' life so fast and free
Try to keep your eyes on me
'Cause this is our beginning
It's our Genesis
Whispers banging down your window
Rumors reaching a crescendo
No humble beginnings, I'm destined for great things
I'm sure you've heard of me by now, woah-oh
Midnight, draw me to the dark side
Daylight, take me on a joyride
My crime is my passion, I'm mayhem in action
I know what day it is
This is our Genesis
You know what time it is? It's our Genesis!
Tell me what time it is! It's our Genesis!
Yeah, you know what time it is? It's our Genesis!
[On-Screen: hololive production COUNTDOWN LIVE 2025 -> 2026]
[On-Screen: COUNTDOWN LIVE 2025]
[On-Screen: 2nd STAGE]
君に届けたい
I want to reach you
id:entity
ステージに一歩を 踏み出した
I took a step onto the stage
おはよう! こんばんは! と
Good morning! Good evening!
世界に 叫んでみよう
Let's shout it out to the world!
本日のライブでは
For today's live performance,
どれの自分を見せるの?
which side of myself should I show?
前からそう悩んで
I've been worrying about it for so long,
好きな自分になれない
unable to become the self that I like.
そしてある日 誰かに言われた
And then one day, someone said to me...
痛い言葉なんかに 迷っていた
I was lost in those hurtful words
いつも映る笑顔
So that I won't lose...
失わないように
...the smile that is always reflected.
これ以上は 期待を
I decided not to betray...
裏切らないと決めた
...expectations anymore.
溢れている雑音の中で
Amidst the overflowing noise,
この声響けるか?
can this voice of mine resonate?
心に宿る 声を聞いてみよう
Let's listen to the voice dwelling inside my heart.
これはずっと見せたい 自分だった
This is the self I've wanted to show all along.
集まった声たちが
The gathered voices...
ひとつになる id:entity
...become one id:entity!
日々が過ぎて やっとスポットライトに
As the days pass, I finally stand in the spotlight,
立てるけれど少しだけ 怖くなった
but it got just a little scary.
でもね! 一人じゃない
But you see! I am not alone,
仲間たちがいるんだ
I have my companions with me.
家族みたいな絆で
With a bond just like a family,
違いが分かり合えた
we were able to understand our differences.
それぞれの輝きがあって
Each of us has our own unique shine,
ハーモニー奏でるから
so let's play our harmony together!
手をつないで 共に夢のその先へ
Hand in hand, let's head towards the future of our dreams.
精一杯 歓声を上げよう
Let's give it our all and raise our voices in cheer!
幸せを届けるんだ
We will deliver happiness!
どこにだって響けよ
Resonate everywhere!
新しい舞台に
Into a brand new stage,
飛び込んで
...we dive!
流れ星と歪なあの星
A falling star and that warped luminary...
重なる面影に寄り添う そっと君に寄り添う
Cuddling up to overlapping shadows, gently cuddling up to you...
ID:Entityのハーモニーになって
Becoming the harmony of ID:Entity.
心の迷いが消えていく
The hesitation in my heart is fading away.
これからずっとこの自分のままで
From now on, forever as my true self,
集まった声たちが違っても
even if these gathered voices differ,
揺るがないと信じて
I believe they won't waver.
一つになる アイデンティティ
Becoming one... Identity!
Sama-sama, guys semua!
You're welcome, everyone!
お疲れ様でした！
Thank you for your hard work!
Sama-sama, kawan semua!
You're welcome, all my friends!
また会う日まで！
Until the day we meet again!
我ら、エデンの星を統べるもの。秘密結社holoX！
We are the ones who rule the star of Eden. Secret Society holoX!
見参！
We have arrived!
時は満ちた！2026年を待つ貴様ら、準備はいいか！
The time has come! You bastards waiting for 2026, are you ready?!
Are you ready?
夜が深まる ほら Darkness
The night deepens, look, Darkness.
ノワールな罠をぽんとデコる
Decorating a black trap so easily.
我が意に従え 脳内スピン
Obey my will, brain spin.
ござるにござる サムライガール
I am a samurai girl, gozaru!
夜更かししないけど
I don't stay up late, but...
ルーペと手帳でしょ？
A magnifying glass and organizer, right?
助手くん 助手くん
Joshu-kun, Joshu-kun!
切り裂く 悪党 退治 退治
Slashing down the villains, exterminate, exterminate!
悪の手のひら
The palm of evil...
踊りたくなる
makes me want to dance.
ほら 君も
Look, you too...
気づけば ノリノリで
before you know it, are grooving!
どうしようもない
It's inevitable.
押し寄せていく運命
This surging destiny...
抗いようがない
there's no resisting it.
もう全部 塗り替えよう
Let's repaint everything now!
エクスとエクスとエクスとエクスが 交差する真ん中で
Where ex, ex, ex, and ex cross, right in the center,
ネクスト ネクスト ネクスト ネクスト 新しい世界はもう始まってる
next, next, next, next, the new world has already begun!
跳びだせ 跳びだせ 闇が呼ぶ方へ
Leap out, leap out, towards where the darkness calls,
暗黒のエクスデス
the pitch-black Exdes.
混沌としたこの世界を、我ら holoX の色に塗り替えるのだ！
We shall repaint this chaotic world in the colors of holoX!
皆の者、刮目せよ！
Everyone, watch closely!
Yes, My Dark！
Yes, My Dark!
アブソリュート・ダークネス・インフィニティ！
Absolute Darkness Infinity!
我らこそ 世界征服！
We represent world domination!
マダム・ホークアイ！
Madame Hawkeye!
はい、今見てる皆さんは、もう holoX 派ですよ！
Yes, everyone watching right now is already on holoX's side!
コヨリニュームボム！
Koyorinium Bomb!
2026年も、ずっと一緒だよね？
We'll be together forever in 2026 too, right?
天下無双で、鏡開き！
Peerless under heaven, barrel breaking!
一刀両断、叩き斬る！
Cutting in two with a single stroke!
どうしようもない
It's inevitable.
押し寄せていく運命
This surging destiny...
抗いようがない
there's no resisting it.
もう全部 塗り替えよう
Let's repaint everything now!
刮目せよ！
Watch closely!
エクスとエクスとエクスとエクスが
Where ex, ex, ex, and ex...
交差する真ん中で
...cross, right in the center,
ネクスト ネクスト ネクスト ネクスト 新しい世界はもう始まってる
next, next, next, next, the new world has already begun!
跳びだせ 跳びだせ 闇が呼ぶ方へ
Leap out, leap out, towards where the darkness calls,
笑うのは ほら エクスデス
the ones laughing, look, are Exdes.
エクスデス
Exdes.
最後まで
Until the very end...
楽しんでね！
...enjoy yourselves!
よいお年をー！
Have a happy new year!
Run back 'round
Don't stop now
Up with the moonlight
Down in the street lights
Looking for a spotlight
Making my move
(Woah) I'm running
(Woah) 行こう
(Woah) Let's go!
Days like a whirlwind
Don't stop coming
Got me in a tailspin
What can I do?
(Woah) Keep running
(Woah) 行こう
(Woah) Let's go!
Lost and found, back to where I started
I won't stay down, trust me, I can do it
I live life loud, take it to the limit
So stand up proud, now I'm gonna sing it
Run back 'round, it's a new beginning
I run back 'round, got to keep believing
I run back 'round, I know where I'm going
I run back 'round, nothing's gonna stop me now
Woah... I'm gonna run back 'round
Sparks on the pavement
Dreams in the distance
Gotta be relentless
Faster than sound
(Woah) Keep running
(Woah) 行こう
(Woah) Let's go!
Lock it and load it, 僕らは explosive
Lock it and load it, we are explosive!
Swifter and lighter, 明日もきっと brighter
Swifter and lighter, tomorrow will surely be brighter!
Faster than lightning, about to get exciting
Keep on running... Everybody, let's go!
Run back 'round, it's a new beginning
I run back 'round, got to keep believing
I run back 'round, I know where I'm going
I run back 'round, nothing's gonna stop me now
Woah... I'm gonna run back 'round
走って 走って 走って
Run! Run! Run!
I'm gonna run back 'round!
始まるよ！
It's beginning!
終わらない...
Never ending...
We got a dream to share!
I'm gonna run back 'round!
Everybody, come on! I'm gonna run back 'round!
Hello! Are you guys ready?
To greet the new year, hell yeah!
No time to waste! Let's get it started!
単純な phrase で catch して
Catching it with a simple phrase,
困難だらけの人生だけど
though life is full of difficulties.
縦横無尽に slap して楽しんじゃおう
Let's slap freely in all directions and just have fun!
Ah oh, ah oh... (Fly like a feather, soaring high!)
立ちはだかる壁なんて 3秒で knock out
Any wall standing in our way, we'll knock it out in 3 seconds!
(Fly like a feather, soaring high!)
止まらないんじゃなくて 止まれないんだ！
It's not that we won't stop, we can't stop!
Slap by step で空中散歩 私なりで
Slap by step, walking on air in my own way,
隙あらばその瞬間に完全掌握
seizing complete control the moment there's an opening.
沼にハマっちゃうぞ！
You're gonna fall deep into the swamp!
One, two, three で深層心理 crash して
Crashing your deep psyche on one, two, three,
ツマらない現実を
this boring reality...
常識外れの rifle で撃ち抜いて！
Shoot right through it with an unconventional rifle!
今すぐね、世界を見せる！
Right now, I'll show you the world!
ah 極彩色のdance floor
ah, a dance floor in vivid colors
とんだ無礼ね平手打ちよ
what a cheeky move, a slap in the face
子供扱いしないで
don't treat me like a child
ニヤついた顔にslash it！
slash that smirking face!
(clap your hands and stand up, please！)
首飛んじゃっても為せば成る
even if your head flies off, if you do it, it will happen
それがtheoryさ
that's the theory
(clap your hands and stand up, please！)
つべこべ言わず着いてきて
without complaining, come along
ready？
it’s time for the show
we’re ignited
and have no fear
ready to break through.
姿
appearances
形は
shapes
違っても
even if they are different
同じ想いだ
our feelings are the same
そうだから…！
yes, that's why...!
slap by stepで空中散歩私なりで
taking a stroll in the air step by step, in my own way
隙あらばその瞬間に完全掌握
seizing the moment whenever there’s a chance
沼にハマっちゃうぞ！
i'm going to get stuck in the swamp!
one two threeで深層心理crashして
crash into deep psychological layers with one two three
今すぐね
right now
私達の色に染め上げた世界を見せる！
show the world we've dyed in our colors!
皆様！今年の応援もありがとうですわ！
Everyone! Thank you for your support this year!
ホロライブIDはもっともっと盛り上がるよ！
Hololive ID is going to get even more exciting!
ずっと見ててね！来年もよろしくお願いします！
Keep watching us! We look forward to your support next year too!
よいお年を！
Have a great new year!
うほん、皆さん！森カリオペです！
Ahem, everyone! This is Mori Calliope!
What's up, Hololive English -Myth- coming right at you for a brand new year!
今年すごい盛り上がったね！
This year was super exciting!
来年もよろしく！
We look forward to next year too!
We're gonna rock the world ten times harder next year. You in? Next up, Ina!
Ah, hello everyone! This is Ina!
Thank you so much for a really fun 2025!
今年、凄く楽しかったです！
This year was really fun!
来年もよろしくお願いしますね！
We look forward to next year too!
Yeah, let's go! Next is Kiara!
キキリカ、小鳥遊キアラです！
Kikiriki, this is Takanashi Kiara!
来年もよろしく！盛り上げるぞー！
Look forward to next year too! Let's pump it up!
行くぜ！イエス、カモン！
Let's go! Yes, come on!
Yeah, let's go!
Let's have fun in 2026!
Let's go! やってやりましょうか！
Let's go! Let's do this!
2026年もよろしく！
Look forward to 2026 too!
Alright, let's show them what we got!
There's an answer out there somewhere / When the muses whisper 'truth or dare'
Hands are played, lights are low / But no one's keeping score
Set your goals and be tenacious / Cause the future is a game of chance
Chips are down, but I'm gonna win / I play until I win
I'm not gonna give up now / The wheels of fortune circle back around
A future in the betting ring / A maze of outcomes drawing the golden string
And through this tangled thread / I see what's up ahead
A wild chase
A steady pace
Got to try my luck, I'm spinning fate
Spin the wheel, let's see where it falls / Testing the limits and betting it all
Round and round, jumping into the circle / Over and over, the dust will settle
Though the game is never easy / And the outcome is a mystery
But these are fates we're betting on / Perfect, unbroken
Caught alive / By wax and string
Tied us together / At the start of everything
I'm not gonna give up yet / Spin back around with every chance I get
Tears in the silent past,
The time has come for fate to change at last.
And if it's black or red, I'm moving up ahead.
A perfect turn, a staring dance,
A spin of red, I'll face it with my eyes ahead.
La la la la la
I'm taking fate into my hands!
Whoa, yeah!
After this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead.
Hyper jumpin' now!
Hyper jumpin'!
飛び出そう
Let's jump out!
Come on baby
輝いて
Shining bright!
ハートきゅんって pump it up
My heart is going kyun, pump it up!
Hyper jumpin'!
指の先まで
To the tips of your fingers,
もっともっと刺激が欲しいの
I want more and more excitement!
Hyper jumpin' now!
Hyper jumpin'!
子供くらいはしゃぐ方がお徳でしょ
It's more rewarding to play like a kid, right?
低気圧から這い上がっていくテンション
My tension climbing up from low pressure!
酔いながら打ち返し まくるメンション
While riding the high, replying to all the mentions!
カートを乗りこなして進むミッション
Driving the cart, moving forward with the mission!
このままスピード加速して
Just like this, accelerating our speed,
たどり着く先に何があるんだろう
what will be waiting at our destination?
止まらない気持ちは
Our unstoppable feelings...
助走つけて次元を超えて行こう さぁ
will get a running start, let's transcend dimensions!
Hyper jumpin'!
飛び跳ねよう
Let's jump and leap!
ハイになって灰になるまで
Until we get high and burn to ashes,
ダンシング shake it up!
dancing, shake it up!
Hyper jumpin'!
空の向こうまで
To the other side of the sky,
もっともっと近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer!
ドキドキしたい gimme gimme gimme 愛
I want to feel my heart pound, gimme gimme gimme love!
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher and higher!
Hyper jumpin' now!
Hyper jumpin'!
斜めから攻めて解決Q(クエスチョン)
Attacking from an angle to solve the question!
ネガティブを切り裂いてくれるチェンソー
A chainsaw to rip apart all the negativity!
流れるコメントと掛け合いセッション
An interactive session with the flowing comments!
エイムを鍛えて狙い撃つ flick shot
Honing our aim and firing off a flick shot!
dis は no no
Disrespect is a no-no!
好きなら more more more
If you like it, show it more, more, more!
邪魔するノイズは打ち消せ bang bang bang
Shoot down the distracting noise, bang bang bang!
遊びたいだけ
We just want to play!
アンチは無視して笑い飛ばして
Ignore the haters, laugh it off,
蹴飛ばせ kick it!!
and kick them away, kick it!!
このまま僕らは旅をして保存
Just like this, we'll go on a journey,
たどり着く先に何があるんだろう
what will be waiting at our destination?
信じた未来とリンクして保存
Linking up with the future we believed in,
次元を超えて行こう さぁ
let's transcend dimensions!
Hyper jumpin'!
飛び越えよう
Let's jump across!
我らの夜に 帰り
Return to our night...
鏡に映る
Reflected in the mirror...
心に宿っている
...dwelling in my heart...
小さい光
...is a tiny light.
そう 今も感じる
Yes, I still feel it,
どこか心の奥で
somewhere deep in my heart,
目を覚ました
it has awakened.
忘れられない 深い眠り
An unforgettable deep sleep...
今の自分になる その前に
...before I became who I am today.
果てのない 音色で迷い
Wandering in an endless melody...
そして黄昏が 落ちていく
And then the twilight falls...
どこまでも
...limitlessly.
引き締める鎖がまた 体を止めていた
The tightening chains were holding my body back again,
ためらいを覚えてしまって 凍えていくの
realizing my hesitation, I'm freezing up.
明日の向こう側には 未知なるエリア
On the other side of tomorrow lies an unknown area,
その境界線の先に待つのは
and what lies beyond that borderline...
異次元のハジマリ
...is the beginning of another dimension!
不敵に笑う
Laughing fearlessly...
奈落の底へ 落ちていく
...I fall to the bottom of the abyss.
小さな感傷も知らぬ
Without knowing even a tiny sentiment...
時計の針の上
...on the hands of the clock.
記憶に残り 広がる海
The ocean that remains in my memory spreads wide,
届かなかった 知らない森の中に
inside an unknown forest that I couldn't reach.
宇宙を超え 逃げ場所探して
Crossing the universe, searching for a place to escape...
そんな過去もまだ 頭に響いている
...that past is still echoing in my head.
解けない鎖を断ち 切れないままもがき
Struggling without being able to break the unbreakable chains,
物語の始まり 探し続けたい
I want to keep searching for the start of the story.
夢中 いつも不可解な 謎のようなことさ
Obsessed, it's always an unfathomable, riddle-like thing,
この身体の中で目覚めた
that has awakened inside this body...
本当の姿
...my true self!
運命のカードが占う ためらい
The cards of fate divine my hesitation...
真相を 思いのまま
...and truth as I please.
惑わない
I won't doubt!
解き放つ鎖が消え 進めると信じて
Believing I can move forward as the released chains vanish,
新たな自分になって 光の方へ
becoming a new self, heading towards the light.
辿り着いた 未知なるエリア
I've reached the unknown area,密なるエリア,
その境界線を越える日が来た
the day to cross that borderline has come!
異次元のハジマリ
The beginning of another dimension!
信じ合える仲間と一緒に
Together with friends we can believe in,
挑戦の狼煙を上げよう 終わらない
let's raise the signal fire of challenge, that never ends!
青春アーカイブ
Seishun Archive!
まずは集中 邪念は捨てて 平常心
First, concentrate! Cast away idle thoughts and keep a calm mind!
みんなで揃えれば無敵じゃん
If we're all together, we're invincible, right?!
逃げるな 水滴 がんばれ落ちて
Don't run away, water droplets, hang in there and fall!
青春 感じているまま 勝負
Feeling our youth, it's a showdown!
あっちゅう間に 成長した姿を見せたい
In the blink of an eye, I want to show you how much I've grown
リハーサルは完璧 本番はもっと 全力で
Rehearsal was perfect; the real performance will be even more, with all our might!
大切な思い出に
They will probably become...
なってしまうのだろうけどね まだ
...precious memories, but not yet!
感傷に浸ってる暇はない
There's no time to be sentimental
今世紀最大級の夏が始まる
The greatest summer of this century is starting!
Woah~ 想像の果てにある高み
Woah~ The heights at the end of imagination
Woah~ 勝ち獲った景色は尊い
Woah~ The scenery we won is precious
Woah~ 逃げるな 限界の壁越えて
Woah~ Don't run away, cross the wall of limits!
Woah~ 僕らはまだチャレンジャー
Woah~ We are still challengers!
潤んだ 幾重に溺れたって
Even if we drown in the damp layers
確かなノイズを手繰り寄せるように
As if pulling in the certain noise
期待外れだと誰かが嘆く
Someone laments that it's disappointing
痛いと痛いがいつも戦う
Pain and pain are always fighting
プライドだけを頼りに抗う
Resisting, relying only on pride
自分を信じたい
I want to believe in myself
努力は報われる
Effort is rewarded
笑いたい奴は笑ってろ
Let those who want to laugh, laugh!
感傷に浸ってる暇はない
There's no time to be sentimental
今世紀最大級の夏が始まる
The greatest summer of this century is starting!
Woah~ 反響が足りない もっともっと
Woah~ The echo isn't enough, more, more!
Woah~ 後悔はさせない
Woah~ I won't let you regret it
Woah~ 想像の果てにある高み
Woah~ The heights at the end of imagination
Woah~ 勝ち獲った景色は尊い
Woah~ The scenery we won is precious
Woah~ 逃げるな 限界の壁越えて
Woah~ Don't run away, cross the wall of limits!
Woah~ 僕らはまだチャレンジャー
Woah~ We are still challengers!
重ねた手はぎゅっと離さずに
Hold our joined hands tight and don't let go
行くよ 行こう 夢見る空へ
Let's go, let's go to the sky we dream of!
窓越しに見上げた
Looking up through the window
とても小さな空
At the very small sky
ここで出会えたのは
That we were able to meet here
数え切れない奇跡
Is a countless miracle
繰り返した一歩が
Each step we repeated
きらめきを繋いで
Connected the sparkles
星のような笑顔
A star-like smile
導いた
Guided us
Day by day
みんなの声が力になる
Everyone's voices become our strength
Stage by stage
ここでそれぞれ目指すもの
Here, what each of us aims for...
それぞれ描くもの
...what each of us paints...
それぞれ願った夢へ
...to the dream each of us wished for
重ねた手はぎゅっと離さずに
Hold our joined hands tight and don't let go
ひとりひとり違う色で
Each and every one of us, in different colors,
描き出すときめき
Drawing out the excitement
振り向くことなく真っ直ぐに
Straight ahead without looking back
行くよ 行こう 夢見る空へ
Let's go, let's go to the sky we dream of!
笑い合ったことや
The times we laughed together,
尽きない悩み
And our endless worries,
思い出いっぱいなのに
Even though they're full of memories...
ああ 憂鬱な日々
Ah, gloomy days...
上書きじゃなくって
Instead of overwriting,
名前つけて保存
save it as a new file.
どれも全部大事って言い切れる
I can confidently say they're all precious.
One for...
みんなのタネが力になる
Everyone's seeds will become our strength.
All for...
今日もにやけすぎるくらい
Today as well, to the point of smiling too much,
笑顔がもう止まらない
my grin just won't stop.
想いは膨らんでいく
These feelings are swelling up!
重ねた今 ぎゅっと噛み締めた
Reflecting deeply on this moment we've layered together,
一人一人違う声で歌えば ほら広がる
look how it spreads when we sing with our unique voices.
風を感じたら まっすぐに
Once we feel the breeze, straight ahead,
いくよ（いこう）夢見る空へ
here I go! (Let's go!) To the dreaming sky!
憧れて手を伸ばし
Longing for it, reaching out my hand,
掴みとったその光だ
that's the light I grasped!
いつの日か
Someday...
また誰かの憧れに変わる
...it will change into someone else's aspiration.
繋ぐよ
We'll pass it on!
重ねた手はぎゅっと離さずに
Holding our joined hands tightly without letting go,
一人一人違う色で描き出す ときめき
tracing our excitement, each with our own unique colors.
出会ったすべてにありがとう
Thank you for everything we've met.
奇跡だって起こし続け
Continuing to make even miracles happen,
ずっとずっとそばにいるよ
I'll be by your side forever and ever.
いくよ（いこう）夢見る空へ
Here I go! (Let's go!) To the dreaming sky!
ホロライブゲーマーズ！
Hololive Gamers!
いくよ！ / フブキングだよー！
Here we go! / It's Fububking!
みんなお待たせ！
Sorry to keep you waiting, everyone!
We are GAMERS!!!!
楽しむ準備は？ / できてるよね！
Are you ready to have fun? / You are, right!
せーの、We are GAMERS!!!!
Ready, set, We are GAMERS!!!!
こんこん！
Konkon!
はいっ 狐が通ります 白髪ケモ耳白上フブキでーす！
Yes! A fox is passing through. White-haired, animal ears, it's Shirakami Fubuki!
突っ込んじゃって始まらない 君はすこん部に入部しなさい！
Can't get started without throwing in a retort! You, join the Sukon-bu!
はい！(イェイ！) はい！(イェイ！)
Yes! (Yay!) Yes! (Yay!)
コポコポとお茶どうぞ
Pour pour, please have some tea.
ゲームじゃないし 特技はMC
It's not gaming, my special skill is MCing!
明るい やりきる 笑顔が推し！
Cheerful! Giving it her all! You'll love my smile!
みおーん！
Mio-n!
うち うち うちだよ 大神ミオだよ 黒髪ケモ耳狼ミオ！
It's me, me, me, I'm Ookami Mio! Black-haired, animal ears, Ookami Mio!
ツッコミで止めます 霊感も 笑い出すと止まらない ゲラゲラ
Stopping things with a retort, plus my sixth sense... Once I start laughing, I can't stop! Chuckle, chuckle!
つまり実はポンってことで どう？
So in other words, I'm actually a klutz. How's that?
立ち位置 セクシー担当
My position is the sexy one!
タロット占いで見る未来 ホラゲはやりたくない！
Reading the future with tarot cards... I don't wanna play horror games!
4人そろえば まず最強 君も朝昼晩 ピッタリ
With the four of us gathered, we're first of all the strongest! You, too, morning, noon, and night, a perfect fit!
クリアを目指して レベル上げ 今日は 何プレイしよう？
Aiming to clear, levelling up! What shall we play today?
君のハートも 攻略しちゃう 選択をして シミュレーション
We'll even conquer your heart! Make a choice and simulate!
初見もカスタムも 大乱闘 やっぱり ゲームは楽しいね
First playthroughs, customs, and grand brawls! After all, games are fun!
G-A-M-E-R-S
We are GAMERS!!!!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
いつももぐもぐ猫又おかゆ おにぎり おにぎり はいどうぞ
Always munching, Nekomata Okayu! Onigiri, onigiri, here you go!
キラキラフラフラ しょうがない猫だもん ん？ そっか 僕でよくない？
Sparkling, wandering, can't be helped, after all I'm a cat! Hmm? I see. Isn't it fine if it's me?
まったりゆっくり 跳ねるリズム 全肯定する おかゆイズム
Chilled out, slow, bouncing rhythm. Unconditionally accepting Okayu-ism.
全肯定コール 準備オッケー？ 毎日僕と一緒に...
Unconditional acceptance call, ready? Every day together with me...
ころね！
Korone!
おはよー！ゆびゆびー！わぉーん！ わんわんころね 犬神ころね
Good morning! Yubi yubi! Woof! Woof woof Korone, Inugami Korone!
キャバリアキングチャールズスパニエル なつくけど凶暴的
Cavalier King Charles Spaniel, gets attached but is ferocious!
訛るイントネーション ワイルドなリアクション まずは指を捧げてくれる？ はい よいしょ！
Dialect intonation, wild reaction! First, will you offer me your fingers? Yes, yoisho!
わかったなー？ おかわり地獄オッケー！ 好物のレタスをあげよう お裾分け
Got it? Refill hell, okay! I'll give you my favorite lettuce to share!
4人揃えば 結末最強
If the four of us gather, the end result is the strongest!
フラグ立てれば即回収
If we raise a flag, we immediately resolve it
エイム鍛えて狙い撃ち
Train our aim and shoot on target
今日は何プレイしよう？
What shall we play today?
君のハートを回復しちゃう
We'll heal your heart
ワクワクするね このダンジョン
How exciting, this dungeon!
耐久って言うか 辞められない
Is it an endurance run? I can't stop
だってゲームが好きなんだもん
Because we just love games!
突然ですが、ボーナスチャレンジの時間です！
Suddenly, it's time for a bonus challenge!
大きな声でレスポンスして、高得点を狙いましょう！
Respond with a loud voice and let's aim for a high score!
Are you ready?
せーの、コーンコーン！
One, two, Kon, kon!
コーンコーン！
Kon, kon!
せーの、みょんみょん！
One, two, Myon, myon!
みょんみょん！
Myon, myon!
せーの、もぐもぐ！
One, two, Mogu, mogu!
もぐもぐ！
Mogu, mogu!
せーの、ゆびゆび！
One, two, Yubi, yubi!
ゆびゆび！
Yubi, yubi!
せーの、コーンコーン！
One, two, Kon, kon!
コーンコーン！
Kon, kon!
せーの、みょんみょん！
One, two, Myon, myon!
みょんみょん！
Myon, myon!
せーの、もぐもぐ！
One, two, Mogu, mogu!
もぐもぐ！
Mogu, mogu!
せーの、ゆびゆび！
One, two, Yubi, yubi!
ゆびゆび！
Yubi, yubi!
合格！
Success!
おおー！
Oh!
4人揃えば 結末最強
If the four of us gather, the end result is the strongest!
上手くいかなくても コンティニュー
Even if it doesn't go well, continue!
リスナーの前で 諦めない
In front of the listeners, we won't give up...
エンディングを見に行こう
Let's go see the ending!
君のハートも 攻略しちゃう
We'll capture your heart too
選択をして シミュレーション
Make a choice and simulate
初見殺しも 乗り越えろ
Overcome the first-time traps
やっぱりゲームは 楽しいね
After all, games are fun!
We are GAMERS!
こうして2025年の幕が閉じるのであった
And so, the curtain closed on the year 2025.
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heartbeats echo
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
With the best of times and the best of friends
キラメキに乗って☆
Ride on the sparkle☆
イェーイ！
Yeah!
覚えてるかな？ 最初の歌
Do you remember our very first song?
懐かしいね
How nostalgic
私 声が震えていた
My voice was trembling back then
ほんの少し
Just a little bit
あの日から続く未来は
The future that has continued since that day...
みんなと掴んだ今日だよ
Is this day that we seized together!
もっともっともっともっと 加速するハート
More, more, more, more, my accelerating heart
いっしょに
Together
行くよ どこまでも
Let's go anywhere!
Are you ready?
準備はおっけー？
ひらけ！！ 夢のトビラを
Open!! The door to our dreams
1 2 3
キラメキライダー☆
Kirameki Rider☆
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heartbeats echo
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
With the best of times and the best of friends
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
We're here because you found us
きみに会いたくて やってきたんだ
I came here because I wanted to see you
みんなで歌おう
Let's sing together
終わらないメロディ
A never-ending melody
キラメキに乗って☆
Ride on the sparkle☆
届いているかな？ 私の声
Is it reaching you? My voice
はっきりと
Clearly
届けたいのは きみに笑顔
What I want to deliver to you is a smile
そのスマイル
That smile
理想の遠さに 悔しくて
Feeling frustrated by how far our ideals are...
みんなと泣き笑ったね
We cried and laughed together with everyone
ぎゅっとぎゅっとぎゅっとぎゅっと 全て抱きしめて
Hugging, hugging, hugging, hugging everything tight
いっしょに
Together
行こう どこまでも
Let's go anywhere!
Are you ready?
準備はおっけー？
進め 希望の道を
Go forward, along the path of hope
1 2 3
キラメキライダー☆
Kirameki Rider☆
好きな気持ちから フルに奏でたいな
From our feelings of love, I want to play to the fullest
最高の場所 最高の仲間と
With the best of places and the best of friends
ここにいるよ マボロシなんか...
We're here, it's not some illusion...
...じゃない
...not a hallucination!
君の心が幸せに染まるように
So that your heart will be dyed with happiness,
重ねてくハーモニー
Wearing the harmony we've layered,
キラメキ纏って☆
riding on the sparkle ☆
歌い続けたいな
I want to keep singing,
踊り続けたいな
I want to keep dancing,
そんな願いや わがままもいいでしょ？
Such wishes and selfishness are fine, right?
だって楽しすぎて！もうとまらない！！
Because it's too fun! I can't stop anymore!!
輝くステージでもっともっと！！
On the shining stage, more, more!!
ずっと！！
forever!!
嬉しい 楽しい 愛しい だけじゃ語れない
I can't just talk about happiness, fun, and love
今も 今も 悩みはあるけど
Even now, even now, I have worries, but
ここにいるよ 私 ここにいるよ
I'm here, I'm here,
君と同じ世界を見つめて
looking at the same world as you,
キラメキライダー☆
Kirameki Rider☆
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make the newborn heart-pounding sensation resonate
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
With the best time and the best companions,
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
I'm here because you found me,
君に会いたくてやって来たんだ みんなで歌おう
I came here because I wanted to meet you, let's sing with everyone
終わらないメロディ キラメキに乗って☆
An unending melody, riding on the sparkle ☆
キラメキ纏って☆
Wearing the sparkle ☆
Yeah!
2025年もあと少し！
Only a little bit left of 2025!
みんな盛り上がってる？
Is everyone excited?!
今回はカウントダウンライブ！
This time is the Countdown Live!
あれあれ？今回の熱量なんかちょっと少なくない？
Wait, wait? Isn't the enthusiasm a bit low?
まだまだ足りないぞー！
It's still not enough!
このこのこの！このこのこのこの！
This, this, this! This, this, this, this!
こにこにこにこにこにこに
Koni-koni-koni-koni-koni-koni!
私のターン！しみじみお仕事励んでくれてありがとう！
It's my turn! Thank you so much for working hard!
もしかしてもしかして愛おしい？
Could it be, could it be that you adore me?
絶対絶対絶対絶対絶対絶対絶対絶対絶対絶対絶対絶対絶対絶対絶対絶対お願いね！
Absolutely, absolutely... please, okay?
このこのこのこの！
This one, this one, this one, this one!
うー！このこのこのこの！
Woo! This one, this one, this one, this one!
このこのこのこのこの！
This one, this one, this one, this one, this one!
銀河の果てまで おしおしおーし！
Even to the ends of the galaxy, support, support, support!
同じ未来を見ていたい
I want to look at the same future...
あの夢手にしたい
...and make that dream ours.
それぞれ違ったココロで
With our own different hearts...
走れ go
...let's run, go!
Shiny Smily Story
[Song: Shiny Smily Story]
どこを見ても真っ暗な場所に芽生えてた
Sprouting in a place where everywhere was pitch black...
ほんの小さな希望に
...was a tiny hope...
この瞳奪われた
...that completely captured my eyes.
不安で揺れる心を上手くチューニングして
Tuning my heart that was shaking with anxiety...
ほんの小さな勇気を
...I summoned up...
振り絞っていたよ
...just a tiny bit of courage.
諦めの文字デリートして進む
I'll move forward, deleting the word "give up".
苦しいときも、もう私はひとりじゃないから
Because even in painful times, I'm no longer alone.
だからもっと夢追いかけたい
So I want to chase my dreams even more,
ワクワク止まらない
this excitement won't stop!
想像超えてく世界見せてあげる
I'll show you a world that exceeds your imagination.
アクセスしてみたい
I want to try accessing it,
後悔なんてそうさせない
I won't let you have any regrets!
それぞれ違ったココロで走れ go
With our own different hearts, let's run, go!
仮想の空に輝く眩しい想いは
The dazzling feelings shining in the virtual sky...
見たことのない光を現実に届けるよ
...will deliver an unseen light to reality!
いつも聞こえるエールはここにキャプチャーして
Capturing the cheers that I always hear right here,
また新しい光を探したくなるよ
it makes me want to search for a new light again.
君の笑顔は保存して進む
I'll save your smile and move forward,
悲しいときに見返すよ
I'll look back at it when I'm sad,
力が湧くから
because it gives me strength.
胸を張って夢追いかけたい
I want to puff out my chest and chase my dreams,
奇跡の物語
this story of miracles!
一緒に作ろう終わらない夢を
Let's create an endless dream together!
誰一人欠かせない
Not a single person is expendable,
愛が舞ったこの世界
in this world where love dances!
それぞれ違ったココロで彩れ
Color it with our own different hearts!
悲しいときも
Even in sad times...
寂しいときも
...and even in lonely times...
信じ合えるものがある
...there is something we can believe in together.
忘れずにこの鼓動
Without forgetting this heartbeat...
鳴らし続けたい
...I want to keep it sounding.
終わらない世界に
Into this endless world...
溢れ出すよ笑顔達
...smiles will overflow!
憧れの舞台立ちたい
I want to stand on the stage of my dreams,
らしく輝きたい
shining in my own unique way.
時に涙して
Sometimes shedding tears,
また笑い合いたい
I want to laugh together again.
同じ未来を見たい
I want to see the same future,
あの夢手にしたい
I want to grasp that dream.
踏み出そう 奇跡の一歩を
Let's take a step forward, a miraculous step!
息切らして夢追いかけたい
Out of breath, I want to chase my dreams,
ワクワク止まらない
this excitement won't stop!
想像超えてく世界見せてあげる
I'll show you a world that exceeds your imagination.
アクセスしてみない？
Why don't you try accessing it?
後悔なんてここにない
There are no regrets here!
それぞれ違ったココロで作る world
A world we create with our own different hearts!
みんな！コークは持ったかな？
Everyone! Do you have your Coke?
持ちました！乾杯する！
We got it! Let's toast!
こらこら、早いよ、ラプラスちゃん！
Hey, too early, La+-chan!
避けるな！ / あたる！
Don't dodge! / It's hitting!
年越しのタイミングで、みんなで乾杯ってするんだよ！
At the turn of the year, we're all going to toast together!
やだやだ！もう喉カラカラ！
No, no! My throat is parched!
ふふ、楽しみだね！
Hehe, I can't wait!
ね？みこさん？みこさん？
Right, Miko-san? Miko-san?
いやー！良いライブだったねー！
Wow! That was a great live show!
お疲れ！ / いぇーい！
Good job! / Yay!
この後どうする？ご飯食べる？
What should we do now? Grab some food?
いやー、どこも混んでんじゃない？
Well, everywhere is probably crowded.
確かに！
True!
もう帰りますかねー。あ、運転手さん、まっすぐね！
I guess we'll head home. Oh, driver, go straight!
お前ら！何帰ってんだ！
You guys! Why are you going home?!
乾杯！乾杯！
Toast! Toast!
フブちゃんたちが付いてきてる！
Fubu-chan and the others are chasing us!
おらおらフブす、寂しくなっちゃったのかね？
My, my, Fubus. Did she get lonely?
待てーーー！
Wait up!
なんか怒ってない？
Doesn't she look kind of mad?
やばい、あの悪戯がバレたかね？
Uh oh, did they find out about that prank?
あははは！やりすぎだったかなー！
Ahahaha! Maybe we went a bit too far!
やばいかも！運転手さん、ごめん！
This might be bad! Driver, sorry!
みこ、ドラテクで逃げるぞ！
Miko's gonna use her drift skills to escape!
うわーーーお！うわーーーお！
Whoaaaa! Whoaaaa!
あ、来た！
Ah, they're here!
すごい！すごい！
Amazing! Amazing!
フブちゃんごめんって！もう悪戯しないから！
Fubu-chan, we're sorry! We won't play pranks anymore!
だめだよみこみこ、反省しなさい！
That's no good, Mikomiko. You must reflect!
お前も共犯だろうが！
You're an accomplice too!
何の話だ？
What are you talking about?
二人ともこれ持って！
Both of you, take this!
何するの？
What are we doing?
もうすぐ新年だよ！
It's almost the New Year!
10！9！
10! 9!
8！7！
8! 7!
6！5！
6! 5!
大きな声で
With a louder voice
未来の僕らに まだ見ぬキミに
To our future selves and to the you I haven't met yet
伝えたいこと沢山あるんだ
There are many things I want to convey
迎えたイマは当たり前なんかじゃない
The present we've reached isn't something to take for granted
翼を広げさあ今
Spread your wings, come on, let's...
飛ぼう！
...fly now!
take my hand！！
Take my hand!
連れて行くよ！光の真ん中
I'll take you to the center of the light
夢の先へ
beyond the dream
羽ばたける勇気はキミの願い
The courage to fly is your wish
皆で繋いだこの奇跡が
This miracle we connected together
途切れないように歌うんだ
I sing so it won't break
もっと高く！大きな声で
With a louder voice
僕らの未来彩って
Coloring our future
どこまでも響け！Prism Melody
Resound everywhere, Prism Melody!
Won't you just forget about the past?
Cause in time it will never matter
But the love we had, I'm hoping it will last
Bersama kita t'lah lewati
Together we have been through it
Tawa dan canda jadi memori
Laughter and jokes became memories
Pastikan artinya kan cerahkan mu nanti
Make sure the meaning will brighten you later
To do what you were meant to do
For it's time to make it true
Together we can always stand
Your hand in my hand
Forever hand in hand
Tuk mulai bermimpi
To start dreaming
Genggam lah yang kau cari
Grab what you're looking for
Teriakkan, la la la la la, la la la la la
Shout out, la la la la la, la la la la la
Kau takkan sendiri
You won't be alone
It's time to show them who you are
Just shout it from the mountain high
To the sky we go, we go
Bersama kita t'lah lewati
Together we have been through it
Tawa dan canda jadi memori
Laughter and jokes became memories
Pastikan artinya cerahkan mu nanti
Make sure the meaning will brighten you later
Cerahkan mu nanti
Will brighten you later
To do what you were meant to do
For it's time to make it true
Together we can always stand
Your hand in my hand
Forever hand in hand
Tuk mulai bermimpi
To start dreaming
Genggam lah yang kau cari
Grab what you're looking for
Teriakkan, la la la la la, la la la la la
Shout out, la la la la la, la la la la la
Kau takkan sendiri
You won't be alone
So go and travel far
Run and show them who you are
I'll be singing, la la la la la, la la la la la
Be who you meant to be
がんばろう！
Let's do our best!
Jangan kau takut
Do not be afraid,
Karena pada akhirnya
because in the end,
Semua kan baik saja
everything will be alright.
Arahkan pandangan mu
Direct your gaze,
Tajam lurus ke depan
sharp and straight ahead.
Tuk mulai bermimpi
To start dreaming,
Genggam lah yang kau cari
hold on to what you are searching for.
Teriakkan
Scream it out!
La la la la la... La la la la la...
Kau takkan sendiri
You won't be alone.
So go and travel far
Run and show them who you are
I'll be singing
La la la la la... La la la la la...
Kau takkan pernah sendiri
You will never be alone.
It's time to show them who you are
Just shout it from the mountain high
To the sky we go, we go, oh!
All for One
Ooh
Just look around and see—it's so incredible!
So many smiles in a sea of light
Take one step with me and you'll be dazzled
There's magic in the air tonight
The hours zoom zoom zoom
My heart goes boom boom boom
The world is brighter because you believe in me
Let's shout it loud loud loud
Our time is right now
We're on the edge of destiny
For a moment, I can dream with you
Every miracle we hoped for might come true
We come together, reaching out from far and wide
And suddenly, you're here by my side!
When our voices and hearts unite, we're gonna shine bright!
Together, we're all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
The thrill of happiness is all around us!
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
Hey!
All that we waited for, the dream we're striving toward
We're singing, all for one!
All for one!
Everything's in motion
Get up and start the celebration
Come see the wonders here beyond imagination
We're joining hands for the world to see
Feel the love and the energy!
The hours zoom zoom zoom
My heart goes boom boom boom
A dizzy whirlwind of dreams and reality
Let's shout it loud loud loud
Our time is right now
We're here together, finally!
Every moment takes my breath away
There's a feeling here that words cannot convey
We hear the rhythm and we rise to meet the song
And suddenly, our hearts beat as one!
Every voice ringing loud and clear, so glad to be here
Together, we're all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
We'll sing in harmony and we'll be happy
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
Keep up the hype, it's good times, good vibes
Remember this night the rest of our lives
Hey!
Raise up your hands and sway, your light will lead our way
We're shining, all for one!
All for one!
So bring your memories, your joy and your hope
We'll gather and we'll sing upon this endless road, oh, oh
Feel the music in your passionate soul
We're here right now, so let the good times roll, oh, oh
Every time that I'm with you
I could swear it's like a wish is coming true
So I'll believe in you if you believe in me
Together we can chase all our dreams!
One, two, three, four, five!
When our voices and hearts unite, we're gonna shine bright!
Together, we're all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
The thrill of happiness is all around us!
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
Hey!
All that we waited for, the dream we're striving toward
We're singing, all for one!
All for one!
All for One!
皆さん、あけましておめでとうございます！
Everyone, Happy New Year!
Flow GlowのViviは？
Where's Vivi of Flow Glow?
寝てます！
She's sleeping!
ここからはホロライブDEV_ISコラボステージです！
From here, it's the Hololive DEV_IS collab stage!
聴いてください、FG ROADSTER by Flow Glow！
Please listen to "FG ROADSTER" by Flow Glow!
Let's go!
搭載V8エンジン 第7感持ってる原人
Packin' a V8 engine and a seventh sense for things
ロックするこの世界と全人類 この5人でゲームをチェンジ
Locking onto this world and all humanity, with us five, we'll change the game
唸る4輪発射セヨ 皆さん3キュー사랑해요
Rev the four wheels and blast off! Thank you all, love you!
操る2台 of turntable 獲る1番ここground 0
Controlling two turntables, we'll take number one right here at ground zero
リスク超えて挑戦 チャンスもセットだ当然
Face the risks and challenge ourselves, opportunities are packaged with them naturally
登り上げる頂点
Climbing all the way to the top
座布団積んでく笑点 乗り込むFG ROADSTER
Stacking cushions on stage, jumping into the FG ROADSTER
特殊部隊集合能力者
A special unit assembled of gifted espers
この歴史に名を彫る彫刻家
Sculptors carving our names into this history
ぶっちぎりで置き去り後続車
Tearing ahead, leaving the other cars far behind in the dust
今高速でぶち抜けていく大気圏
Now speeding and breaking through the stratosphere
エンジンからジェットの炎 揺れている怪気炎
Jet flames from our engine, burning with hot-headed spirit
眼下に広がる大地を越えていく回帰線
Crossing the tropics above the vast earth unfolding below
バックミラーにbig blueが写っているI+B+M
In the rear-view mirror, the big blue of IBM is reflected
打ち上げ台から飛んでく うちら世代この燃料
Taking off from the launch pad, our generation is the fuel
朽ち果てないです 銀河で寿司食べたい
We won't fade away, we wanna eat sushi in the galaxy
見えてるでかいビジョン 燃えてるメンバー一同
Seeing a massive vision, all of us burning with passion
ただいま現在進行形 越えてく世界規模
As of this moment, we are going worldwide
叶うはずだwon't stop 心臓がモンスター
It will come true, won't stop, our hearts are monsters
aliens, turn it up, FG party hard
光るTesla roadster, heavy booster
Shining Tesla roadster, heavy booster
目覚めていく本能 青い炎
Awakening instincts, blue flames
B+F+F, let's go out, so, get in the car
0から宇宙まで囚われず
Unconfined, from zero to space
走るFG ROADSTER, 唸るbooster
Speeding FG ROADSTER, roaring booster
パレード、パレード、パレード！
Parade, Parade, Parade!
探しにゆく
We're going to search...
スタートは何度だって
...for the start, no matter how many times.
ただ 独り言を綴った
I just wrote down a monologue.
ただ 始まりたくて 走った
I just wanted to begin, so I ran.
遠く 暗がりに灯った
Lit up far away in the darkness,
それは 眩し過ぎた名前
that was a name too dazzling.
それは 優し過ぎる思い出
Those were memories too gentle.
もっと 近づけと 手を伸ばした
I reached out my hand to get closer.
思いがけず 結び合った
Unexpectedly, we were tied together.
ほら 今 迷子は
Look, now the lost children...
“僕等”になった
...became "Us."
Parade, Parade, Parade! 輝くんだよ
Parade, Parade, Parade! It shines!
悔しさも 愛しさも 連れておいで
Bring along the regrets and the love.
風、夢、羽 飛び立てるさ
With the wind, dreams, and feathers, we can fly!
ささやかな祈りは 光
A small prayer is light,
終わりなき兆し
an endless omen.
君を見つけたこと 胸を張れるよ
Our Bright Parade, Parade!
That I found you, I can hold my head high.
まだ 頼りない予感を
An uncertain premonition still,
歌おう 恥ずかしくなんて ないよ
let's sing it, there's nothing to be ashamed of.
誰も解けない イマジナリー
An imaginary no one can solve,
いつかまた逢える おまじない
a good luck charm to meet again someday.
あの日のゼロに始まったストーリー Blues
The story that started at zero that day,
数え切れない 言の葉
countless words.
数えるような 想いじゃないさ
It's not a feeling like counting.
ほら 今 “僕等”を
Look, now let's call...
一つと呼ぼう
...\"Us\" one.
Parade, Parade, Parade! 美しいんだよ
Parade, Parade, Parade! It's beautiful!
許し合える刹那 夜はきらめく
The moment we can forgive each other, the night sparkles.
雨、晴れ、カレイド
Rain, sun, kaleidoscope,
またとない空
a sky like no other.
相応しい旅路とは 君と歩くことさ
The appropriate journey is walking with you,
君と歩くことなんだ
it's walking with you.
「ただいま」を聞けば
When I hear "I'm home,"
「おかえり」って叫ぶよ
I'll shout "Welcome back!"
当たり前じゃないか
Isn't that obvious?
Parade, Parade, Parade! 輝くんだよ
Parade, Parade, Parade! It shines!
暗がりを満たすのは 君だ 僕だ
What fills the darkness is you, and me.
Parade, Parade, Parade! 輝くんだよ
Parade, Parade, Parade! It shines!
悔しさも 愛しさも 連れておいで
Bring along the regrets and the love.
風、夢、羽 飛び立てるさ
With the wind, dreams, and feathers, we can fly!
ささやかな祈りは 光
A small prayer is light,
終わりなき兆し
an endless omen.
君と 飛び込んでゆく
Diving in together with you,
素敵なスタートさ
it's a wonderful start.
ここから これから Our Bright
From here, from now, Our Bright...
Parade, Parade!
Our Bright Parade, Parade!
この後は もう1本グランプリ！
2026年もホロライブプロダクションをよろしくお願い致します！
Up next, another Grand Prix!
We look forward to your continued support of hololive production in 2026!